<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Oddly Specific Objects</title><link>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Oddly Specific Objects</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/about/</guid><description>TODO</description></item><item><title>LCD FeatherWing</title><link>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/products/lcdwing/lcdwing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/products/lcdwing/lcdwing/</guid><description>The LCD FeatherWing is a low-power display compatible with Adafruit&amp;rsquo;s Feather line of development boards. It uses the BU9796 segment LCD controller to drive a custom liquid crystal display glass with 48 segments, including:
Five indicator icons: Bell, Wifi, Moon, Arrows and Battery Five 7-segment digits, plus a sign indicator Four decimal points, one between each pair of digits. AM and PM indicators, plus a colon for displaying the time Assembly Instructions TODO</description></item><item><title>Sensor Watch</title><link>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/products/sensorwatch/sensorwatch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/products/sensorwatch/sensorwatch/</guid><description>
Sensor Watch is a board swap for the classic Casio F-91W wristwatch. It brings the power of a Cortex M0+ microcontroller to your wrist, while reusing many elements of the original watch such as its low-power LCD, water-resistant enclosure and beepy piezo buzzer.
Sensor Watch is available on Crowd Supply, with most backer boards shipping in Q3 2022, and new orders shipping in Q1 2023.
Resources for Wearers Sensor Watch Discord channel Assembly video Firmware images Watch face documentation Resources for Developers GitHub repository Watch Interface Guidelines Low-level watch library documentation Discussion dorum Temperature Sensor + GPIO board documentation Sensor board design notes</description></item><item><title>The Open Book</title><link>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/projects/openbook/openbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.oddlyspecificobjects.com/projects/openbook/openbook/</guid><description>The Open Book is my long-standing attempt to design a comprehensible and accessible e-book reader that you can build yourself (or at least have manufactured affordably).
As of 2022, I am dramatically reworking the design based on lessons learned in the last two years. More detail soon.</description></item></channel></rss>